Guide to the Leonid N. Stolovich papers M1624
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 7. Newspapers and magazines
  - "Vpered", 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folders 6)
  - "Vpered", 1989 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - "Vpered", 1989 (Box 23, Folders 7)
  - "Vpered", 1989-1991 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - "Vpered", 1990 (Box 23, Folders 9)
  - "Vpered", 1990 (Box 23, Folders 8)
  - "Vpered", 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folders 1)
  - "Vpered", 1991 (Box 24, Folders 3)
  - "Vpered", 1991 (Box 24, Folders 2)
  - "Za Rubezhom", 1988 (Box 15, Folders 6)
  - Selection of newspapers: "Alma Mater", "Atmoda", "Baltiiskoe Vremia", "Doverie", "Ekspress Khronika", 1989-1992 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Selection of newspapers: "Ekho Litvy","Demokraticheskaia Rossiia", "Interdvizhenie", "Baltiiskaia Gazeta", "Krovavoe Voskresenie", "Novaia Partiia", 1990-1991 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Selection of newspapers": "Novaia Rech", "Respublika", "Soglasie", "Opozitsiia", "Sovetskaia Litva", "Universitas Tartuensis", "Vestnik", 1989-1990 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Random issues of the publications of Jewish organizations: Alef, Tsaadim (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Leaflets, 1988-1990 (Box 144, Folder 8)
- Series 8. Newspaper clippings
  - Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1988, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folders 4)
  - Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folders 3)
  - Clippings, 1989-1993 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folders 5)
  - Clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 14, Folders 1)
  - Clippings, 1990-2001 (Box 14, Folders 2)
  - Clippings, 1992 (Box 13, Folders 10)
  - Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1981-1991 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1981-1991, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1987-2003 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1987-2003 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1987-2003 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1987-2003 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1987-2003 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1987-2003 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Tartu University (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Tartu University (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Tartu University (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Tartu University: Celebration of the 375th Anniversary (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Science (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Science, 1958-1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Lenin on arts (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Lenin on arts (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Art and culture (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Art and science (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Art and science (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Art life (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Art life (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Art life, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Art life, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Art life, 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Art life, 1952-1954 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Art life, 1956-1958 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Art life, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Art life, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Art life, 1960-1961 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Art life, 1960-1961 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Art life, 1962-1963 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Art life, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Art life, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Art life, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Art life, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Art life, 1964-1966 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Art life, 1966-1967 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Art life, 1968-1969 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Art life, 1968-1969 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Art and Perestroika, 1985-1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Art and Perestroika, 1985-1989 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Methodology of aesthetics (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Modernism (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Modernism (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Estonian art and culture (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Akhmadulina, Bella; Voznesenskii, Andrei; Galich, Aleksandr; Visotskii, Vladimir (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Brodsky, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Mandelshtam, Osip; Akhmatova, Anna (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pasternak, Boris (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Sakharov, Andrei Dmitrievich (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Slutskii, Roris; Okudzhava, Bulat; Samoilov, David (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Solzhenitsin, Aleksandr I. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Solzhenitsin, Aleksandr I. (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Yevtushenko, Yevgenii A. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Poets (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Poetry (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Literary criticism (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Literary criticism (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Literary works and culture: re-evaluation of values, 1980-ties (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Writer's Unions (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Music (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Internal politics in Soviet Union, 1948-1956 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Internal politics in Soviet Union, 1957-1958 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Internal politics in Soviet Union, 1950-1967 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Stalin (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Stalin (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Stalin (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Stalin (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Stalin (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Stalin (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Stalin (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Prague Spring and Soviet invasion of Czechoslovakia, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Prague Spring and Soviet invasion of Czechoslovakia, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Prague Spring and Soviet invasion of Czechoslovakia, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Prague Spring and Soviet invasion of Czechoslovakia, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Prague Spring and Soviet invasion of Czechoslovakia, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - 19th Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - 19th Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - 23rd Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - 23rd Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - 26th Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party of Estonia, 1990-1991 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party of Estonia, 1991-1992 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1950-1966 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1956-1958 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1958-1969 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1964-1969 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1983-1989 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1984-1992 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1988-1990 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party and art, 1948-1951 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party and art, 1952-1956 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party and art, 1957-1958 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Communist Party and art, 1958-1959 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Communist Party and art, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party and art, 1970-1980 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Communist Party and art, 1970-1980 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Communist Party and art, 1980-ties (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party and art, 1980-ties (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Union and China (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Dissidents' cases and political immigration: Ginzburg, Belinkov, Matysevich, Kuznetsov, Aksenov, Supeldin, Nekrasov, Kopol etc. (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Estonia on its way to independence (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Estonia on its way to Independence (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Estonia on its way to independence (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Coup d'etat, August 1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Discussions about Perestroika (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Discussions about Perestroika (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Discussions about Perestroika (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Discussions about Perestroika (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Discussions about Perestroika (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Perestroika and problems of history (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Perestroika and problems of history (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Perestroika and national relations (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Russian nationalism and fascist movement (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Russian nationalism and fascist movement (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Anti-semitism, 1990-2004 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Anti-semitism, 1990-2004 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - "Etika", 1971-1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "Religiia i ateism", 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Filosofiia", 1948-1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "Estetika", 1971-1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - "Estetika", 1971-1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Estetika", 1971-1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "Estetika", 1971-1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "Borba s sionizmom v SSSR i sotsialisticheskom lagere", 1963-1983 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "Borba s sionizmom v SSSR i sotsialisticheskom lagere", 1963-1983 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "Borba s sionizmom v SSSR i sotsialisticheskom lagere", 1963-1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - "Pravda": 1938-1938, 1939 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - "Pravda": 1938-1938, 1939 (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - "Partiinye dokumenty", 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "Partiinye dokumenty", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Partiinye dokumenty", 1987Newspaper "Partiinye dokumenty", 1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Partiinye dokumenty", 1987 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "Partiinye dokumenty", 1987Newspaper "Partiinye dokumenty", 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "Partiinye dokumenty", 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - "Partiinye dokumenty" (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "Partiinye dokumenty" (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Aesthetics and the problem of comic (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Soviet aesthetics (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Soviet aesthetics (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Series 9. Audiovisual Materials
  - Recordings of Stolovich's participation in radio and TV etc.: Audiotapes, 4 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Recordings of Stolovich's participation in radio and TV etc.: CD-Rom, 1 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Recordings of Stolovich's participation in radio and TV etc.: TV programs (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Recordings of Stolovich's participation in radio and TV etc.: DVD's, 7 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Recordings of Stolovich's participation in radio and TV etc.: VHS cassettes, 11 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - The 70th birthday anniversary of Lotman Yuri, M. (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - TV programs by Shenderovich, Victor A. (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Samoilov, David: reading of poetry: disc (Flat-box 152, Folder 1)
  - Solzhenitsin, Aleksandr I.: Russian TV programs (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Solzhenitsin, Aleksandr I.: Russian TV programs (Box 147, Folder 5)